A Guide to the Papers of the Norfolk Forum, 1930-
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Papers of the Norfolk Forum 1930-
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
77
17 Hollinger Document Cases, 11 photograph boxes, 1 VHS tape box, and 1 mini-audiocassette box. 11.5 Linear feet
Norfolk Forum (Norfolk, Va.)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Open to researchers without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
On loan from the Norfolk Forum, June 2000.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Norfolk Forum is believed to be the oldest nonprofit, public lecture series in the U.S. Established in 1932 during the Great Depression by Dr. Vincent H. Ober and a handful of other Norfolk citizens, the Norfolk Forum held its first series of lectures during the 1933-34 season. Originally, the Forum was named the "Norfolk Portsmouth Forum of Public Affairs," but it changed its name to the "Norfolk Forum" during its first season. This name and a stellar reputation have stuck with the Norfolk Forum for over 70 years. The Forum incorporated on June 2, 1941.
The Norfolk Forum's first membership drive began the summer before the 1933-34 season, consisting of a booth in the lobby of the Smith and Welton department store as well as requests taken by J.E. Capps, the Forum's president at the time. Approximately, 1,150 persons joined the Norfolk Forum during its first year, exceeding an initial goal of 1,100 people. The cost of a ticket for the first season was only $1. To this day, seasons typically begin in the fall and end in the spring, and usually consist of three to four speakers. The Norfolk Forum only sells season memberships, not tickets to individual speakers.
The Norfolk Forum originally hosted speakers at the 1000 seat auditorium at Blair Junior High School. During the 1936-37 season, two out of the scheduled five speakers were hosted at the City Auditorium, which could seat double this number. The Norfolk Forum used the City Auditorium all of the 1937-38 season, and then returned to Blair Auditorium for the 1938-39 season. They continued using this space until the 1943-44 season. At that time they moved to the new 1,300 seat USO Auditorium, but the Norfolk Forum and the USO could not come to a mutual agreement of terms so the Forum moved back to Blair at the end of that season. Lectures continued at Blair Auditorium until the Fall of 1947. After that time, the Forum moved to the larger Center Theater. In 1972 the Norfolk Forum moved to the 2,481 seat Chrysler Hall and has sponsored speakers in this venue ever since.
The Forum's speakers have included presidents, prime ministers, princes and queens, diplomats, politicians, comedians, writers, journalists, playwrights, poets, correspondents, Pulitzer Prize winners, spies, scientists, adventurers, comedians, musicians, actors and actresses, judges, and many professions too varied to list. Traditionally, male speakers are expected to appear in black tie, as their lecture, often accompanied by a reception, is considered a formal affair.
A board of directors made up of local citizens governs the Norfolk Forum. The Forum is supported entirely by income from ticket sales and a grant from the Bruce Shafer World Peace Fund, which supports one speaker yearly on the topic of world peace.
Scope and Content
The Papers of the Norfolk Forum date from the early 1930's to the present time. Accessions to the collection are received on a regular basis from the Norfolk Forum Historian. The collection contains information about the business of the group, its history, and the numerous speakers sponsored by the Forum. Included are information on the Forum's membership, board of directors, correspondence, committees, policies, calendars and season programs, tickets, brochures, news clippings, and speaker biographies. Also included are audiotapes and videotapes of Forum oral history interviews and select speakers, and numerous photos of various speakers and receptions.
Index Terms
Norfolk Forum (Norfolk, Va.); Nonprofit organizations; Lecturers; Nonprofit organizations; Administrative records; Minutes; Lecturers; Biographies; Interviews; Correspondence; Clippings; Audiotapes; Videotapes; Photographs
Contents List
- Business 1930-
  This series is broken into twelve sub-series related to the business of the Norfolk Forum.
  - Agendas and Minutes 1981-
    This sub-series contains the agendas and minutes from Norfolk Forum Board meetings, as well as meeting announcements. Material dates from 1981 to the present time.
    Chronological
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1981 (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1982 (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1983 (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1984 (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1985 (Box-folder 1:5)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1986 (Box-folder 1:6)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1987 (Box-folder 1:7)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1988 (Box-folder 1:8)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1989 (Box-folder 1:9)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1990 (Box-folder 1:10)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1991 (Box-folder 1:11)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1992 (Box-folder 1:12)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1993 (Box-folder 1:13)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1994 (Box-folder 1:14)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1995 (Box-folder 1:15)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1996 (Box-folder 1:16)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1997 (Box-folder 1:17)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1998 (Box-folder 1:18)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 1999 (Box-folder 1:19)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 2000 (Box-folder 1:20)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 2001 (Box-folder 1:21)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 2002 (Box-folder 1:22)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 2003 (Box-folder 1:23)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes 2004 (Box-folder 1:24)
    - Board Agendas and Minutes -- Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 1:25)
  - Budget and Finances 1945-
    This sub-series contains treasurer's reports from as far back as 1945 up until the present time. Also included are tax returns and various receipts and invoices.
    Alphabetical by topic and then chronologically by year
    - Receipts and Invoices -- Various 1980-1990 (Box-folder 2:1)
    - Tax Return 1993 (Box-folder 2:2)
    - Treasurer's Reports 1945-1946 (Box-folder 2:3)
    - Treasurer's Reports 1980-1990 (Box-folder 2:4)
    - Treasurer's Reports 1990-2000 (Box-folder 2:5)
    - Treasurer's Reports 2000- (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Bylaws and Incorporation 1941, 1990, 1996-1997
    This sub-series contains the Bylaws, Certificate of Incorporation, and related materials of the Norfolk Forum.
    Chronological by year
    - Bylaws 1990 (Box-folder 2:7)
    - Certificate of Incorporation 1941 (Box-folder 2:8)
    - Incorporation Payment and Report 1996-1997 (Box-folder 2:9)
  - Committees 1970-
    This sub-series contains committee agendas, minutes, committee membership lists, correspondence, and other related materials from 1970 onward.
    - Committees 1970-1980 (Box-folder 2:10)
    - Committees 1980-1990 (Box-folder 2:11)
    - Committees 1990-2000 (Box-folder 2:12)
    - Committees -- Ad Hoc Committee on the Future of the Norfolk Forum 2001-2002 (Box-folder 2:13)
    - Committees -- Ad Hoc Committee on the History of the Norfolk Forum 1996-1997 (Box-folder 2:14)
    - Committees -- Ad Hoc Committee on Proposed Student Participation 1996 (Box-folder 2:15)
    - Committees -- Arrangements Committee 1980-1990 (Box-folder 2:16)
    - Committees -- Endowment Committee 1990-2000 (Box-folder 2:17)
    - Committees -- Entertainment Committee 1980-1990 (Box-folder 2:18)
    - Committees -- Long Range Planning Committee 1980-1990 (Box-folder 2:19)
    - Committees -- Nominating Committee 1980-1990 (Box-folder 2:20)
    - Committees -- Nominating Committee 1990-2000 (Box-folder 2:21)
    - Committees -- Nominating Committee 2000- (Box-folder 2:22)
    - Committees -- Program Committee 1980-1990 (Box-folder 2:23)
    - Committees -- Nominating Committee 1990-2000 (Box-folder 2:24)
    - Committees -- Publicity Committee 1980-1990 (Box-folder 2:25)
    - Committees -- Speakers Committee 1990-2000 (Box-folder 2:26)
    - Committees, Responsibilities of undated (Box-folder 2:27)
  - Correspondence and Mailing Lists undated, 1943-
    This sub-series contains general and specific correspondence dating as far back as 1943. It should be noted that various correspondence exists throughout the entire Norfolk Forum collection, not just this sub-series. Much of the correspondence in the Norfolk Forum papers is filed more appropriately under specific topics within other series and sub-series. This sub-series also includes mailing lists and labels, change of address notices, while you were out messages, and information on a computer database for the Norfolk Forum's membership and mailing lists.
    - Board Meeting Absences 1990-2000 (Box-folder 3:1)
    - Board Resignations 1980-1990 (Box-folder 3:2)
    - Board Resignations 1990-2000 (Box-folder 3:3)
    - General Correspondence 1943-1950 (Box-folder 3:4)
    - General Correspondence 1980-1990 (Box-folder 3:5)
    - General Correspondence 1990-2000 (Box-folder 3:6)
    - Letters to Board Members 1980-1990 (Box-folder 3:7)
    - Letters to Board Members 1990-2000 (Box-folder 3:8)
    - Letters to Carter Scott 1989-1997 (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Letters from Marquis Childs 1948-1956 (Box-folder 3:10)
    - Letters Regarding Panhandlers at Chrysler Hall 1994 (Box-folder 3:11)
    - Letters Regarding Program Schedules 1982, 1994 (Box-folder 3:12)
    - Mailing List / Labels undated (Box-folder 3:13)
    - Mailing List Address Changes 1980-1990 (Box-folder 3:14)
    - Mailing List Address Changes 1990-2000 (Box-folder 3:15)
    - Membership / Mailing List Computer Database 1995 (Box-folder 3:16)
    - While You Were Out Messages 1980-1990 (Box-folder 3:17)
    - While You Were Out Messages 1990-2000 (Box-folder 3:18)
    - While You Were Out Messages undated (Box-folder 3:19)
  - Forms and Stationary undated, 1993-1994
    This sub-series contains various forms and stationary including parking passes, speaker contract forms, letterheads, and envelopes.
    Alphabetical by topic
    - Parking Pass Form 1993-1994 (Box-folder 3:20)
    - Parking Signs Reserved for Speakers undated (Box-folder 3:21)
    - Speaker Contracts (blank) undated (Box-folder 3:22)
    - Stationary undated (Box-folder 3:23)
  - Insurance 1990-2000
    This sub-series contains insurance policy information for the Norfolk Forum, as well as material related to specific insurance related incidents.
    - Insurance Policy Certificates, Changes, and Endorsements 1990-2000 (Box-folder 3:24)
    - Insurance Policy Manual 1990-2000 (Box-folder 3:25)
    - Insurance Schedules and Renewals 1990-2000 (Box-folder 3:26)
    - Incident 24 January 1993 (Box-folder 3:27)
    - Incident 5 October 1993 (Box-folder 3:28)
    - Incident 1 May 1994 (Box-folder 3:29)
    - Incident 7 October 1996 (Box-folder 3:30)
  - Membership 1933-1960, 1983-1985, 1995-1998
    This sub-series contains membership lists, member resolutions and appreciations, and other related materials.
    Alphabetical by topic and then chronologically by year.
    - Conflict of Interest -- William Van Buren 1997 (Box-folder 4:1)
    - General Membership Articles 1933-1960 (Box-folder 4:2)
    - Membership List 1983 (Box-folder 4:3)
    - Membership List 1984-1985 (Box-folder 4:4)
    - Member Resolutions / Appreciations 1995-1998 (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Officers and Directors 1930-
    This sub-series contains listings of Norfolk Forum officers, directors, and board members from the 1930's to the present time.
    - Officers 1930-1940 (Box-folder 4:6)
    - Officers and Directors 1940-1950 (Box-folder 4:7)
    - Officers and Directors 1950-1960 (Box-folder 4:8)
    - Officers and Directors 1960-1970 (Box-folder 4:9)
    - Officers and Directors 1970-1980 (Box-folder 4:10)
    - Officers and Directors 1980-1990 (Box-folder 4:11)
    - Officers and Directors 1990-2000 (Box-folder 4:12)
    - Officers and Directors 2000- (Box-folder 4:13)
  - Policies and Procedures undated
    This sub-series contains various policies and procedures for the Norfolk Forum.
    - President's Checklist undated (Box-folder 4:14)
    - Reception Procedures undated (Box-folder 4:15)
    - Ticket Chairman Routine undated (Box-folder 4:16)
  - Subscriptions and Ticket Sales 1960-
    This sub-series contains correspondence and advertisements to subscribers, season ticket purchases from subscribers, copies of Forum tickets and ticket proofs, subscriber surveys, and correspondence related to ticket refunds.
    - Correspondence to Subscribers 1960-1990 (Box-folder 5:1)
    - Correspondence to Subscribers 1990-2000 (Box-folder 5:2)
    - Correspondence to Subscribers 2000- (Box-folder 5:3)
    - Forum Tickets 1980-1990 (Box-folder 5:4)
    - Forum Tickets 1990-2000 (Box-folder 5:5)
    - Forum Tickets 2000- (Box-folder 5:6)
    - Forum Tickets -- Proofs 1990-2000 (Box-folder 5:7)
    - Season Ticket Sales -- Brochures 1980-1990 (Box-folder 5:8)
    - Season Ticket Sales -- Brochures 1990-2000 (Box-folder 5:9)
    - Season Ticket Sales -- Correspondence 1980-1990 (Box-folder 5:10)
    - Season Ticket Sales -- Correspondence 1990-2000 (Box-folder 5:11)
    - Subscriber Surveys 1990-2000 (Box-folder 5:12)
    - Ticket Refunds 1990-2000 (Box-folder 5:13)
  - Miscellaneous Business 199-
    This sub-series contains miscellaneous material related to Norfolk Forum business that did not fit easily under other sub-series.
    Alphabetical
    - Expansion 199- (Box-folder 5:14)
    - Miscellaneous Notes undated (Box-folder 5:15)
- Events 1950-
  This series is broken into five sub-series related to Norfolk Forum Events.
  - Business 1997-1998
    This sub-series contains business items and correspondence specifically related to Norfolk Forum events.
    - Event Parking 1997-1998 (Box-folder 5:16)
    - Pre-Forum Dinner 15 Ocober 1997 (Box-folder 5:17)
  - Calendars 1982, 1996
    This sub-series contains various calendars of interest to the Norfolk Forum. For Norfolk Forum speaker calendars and season programs, see sub-series D: Programs.
    - Arts News Calendar October 1982 (Box-folder 5:18)
    - President's Calendar 1996 (Box-folder 5:19)
  - Invitations 1988, 1994-1997, 1999-2005
    This sub-series contains invitations to Norfolk Forum events and the schedules / programs for these events.
    - Event Invitations and Programs 1988 (Box-folder 6:1)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 1994 (Box-folder 6:2)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 1995 (Box-folder 6:3)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 1996 (Box-folder 6:4)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 1997 (Box-folder 6:5)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 1999 (Box-folder 6:6)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 2000 (Box-folder 6:7)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 2001 (Box-folder 6:8)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 2002 (Box-folder 6:9)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 2003 (Box-folder 6:10)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 2004 (Box-folder 6:11)
    - Event Invitations and Programs 2005 (Box-folder 6:12)
  - Programs 1950-
    This sub-series contains season programs, as well as program drafts, for the Norfolk Forum from the 1950's to the present time.
    - The Norfolk Forum Season Program 1950-1960 (Box-folder 6:13)
    - The Norfolk Forum Season Program 1960-1970 (Box-folder 6:14)
    - The Norfolk Forum Season Program 1970-1980 (Box-folder 6:15)
    - The Norfolk Forum Season Program 1980-1990 (Box-folder 6:16)
    - The Norfolk Forum Season Program 1990-2000 (Box-folder 6:17)
    - The Norfolk Forum Season Program 2000- (Box-folder 6:18)
    - The Norfolk Forum Season Program Drafts 1997-1998 (Box-folder 6:19)
    - The Norfolk Forum Season Program Drafts 1998-1999 (Box-folder 6:20)
  - Receptions 1980-2000
    This sub-series contains correspondence, invoices, schedules, and other information related to Norfolk Forum receptions, including the reception in honor of the Norfolk Forum's 50th Anniversary.
    - 50th Anniversary Reception 1983-1984 (Box-folder 6:21)
    - 50th Anniversary Reception: Prospective Speaker Walter Cronkite 1983-1984 (Box-folder 6:22)
    - Reception Budget 1990-2000 (Box-folder 6:23)
    - Reception Invoices: Cuisine and Company 1995 (Box-folder 6:24)
    - Reception Invoices: Harbor Club 1982, 1987 (Box-folder 6:25)
    - Reception Schedules 1980-1990 (Box-folder 6:26)
    - Reception Schedules 1990-2000 (Box-folder 6:27)
    - Receptions: Various undated (Box-folder 6:28)
- History 1930?-2000?
  This series contains material related to the Norfolk Forum's history. Included are biographies of various members, information and correspondence related to early members in the Norfolk Forum's history, a Norfolk Forum history project and oral histories conducted in the late 1990's, and the drafts and final copies of The Best Ticket in Town: A History of the Norfolk Form.
  - Biographies of Members -- Various undated (Box-folder 6:29)
  - Early Members: Abeles, Charles T. & Mrs. Sally undated (Box-folder 6:30)
  - Early Members: Anderson, Alfred & Mrs. Katherine Hutten undated (Box-folder 6:31)
  - Early Members: Calcott, Mr. & Mrs. A.O. undated (Box-folder 6:32)
  - Early Members: Capps, John E. undated (Box-folder 6:33)
  - Early Members: Chambers, Lenoir undated (Box-folder 6:34)
  - Early Members: Clark, Morton H. undated (Box-folder 6:35)
  - Early Members: Darden, Colgate W., Jr. undated (Box-folder 6:36)
  - Early Members: Dudley, Roy W. undated (Box-folder 6:37)
  - Early Members: Gordon, Conigsby Matheson undated (Box-folder 6:38)
  - Early Members: Harrel, William Lee & Mrs. undated (Box-folder 6:39)
  - Early Members: Harris, Winder R. undated (Box-folder 6:40)
  - Early Members: Hoffman, Walter E. undated (Box-folder 6:41)
  - Early Members: Jaffe, Louis I. undated (Box-folder 6:42)
  - Early Members: Martin, Roy undated (Box-folder 6:43)
  - Early Members: Mendoza, Dr. Louis undated (Box-folder 6:44)
  - Early Members: Newby L.L. undated (Box-folder 6:45)
  - Early Members: Nottingham, Cherry undated (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Early Members: Ober, Dr. Vincent Hilles undated (Box-folder 7:2)
  - Early Members: Scott, Glenn undated (Box-folder 7:3)
  - Early Members: Tunstall Whit P. undated (Box-folder 7:4)
  - Early Members: Tyler, Stockton Heth undated (Box-folder 7:5)
  - Early Members: Van Buren, William R., III undated (Box-folder 7:6)
  - Early Members: Wagenheim, Michael undated (Box-folder 7:7)
  - Early Members: Whitehurst, Dr. G. William undated (Box-folder 7:8)
  - Historian 1990-2000 (Box-folder 7:9)
  - History of the Forum: Articles, Copies, and Notes 1990-2000 (Box-folder 7:10)
  - History Project 1998 (Box-folder 7:11)
  - History Project: Correspondence 1995-1998 (Box-folder 7:12)
  - Oral History Release Forms 1997 (Box-folder 7:13)
  - Photo Requests undated (Box-folder 7:14)
  - Publication of the Forum's History: Expenses 1997-1998 (Box-folder 7:15)
  - The Best Ticket in Town: Draft undated (Box-folder 8:1)
  - The Best Ticket in Town: Draft II undated (Box-folder 8:2)
  - The Best Ticket in Town: Sales and Promotion undated (Box-folder 8:3)
  - The Best Ticket in Town: A History of the Norfolk Forum undated (Box-folder 8:4)
    5 copies
- Publicity 1930-
  This series is broken into three sub-series relating to advertising and media coverage of the Norfolk Forum and its events.
  - Brochures 1990
    This sub-series contains copies of Norfolk Forum brochures, brochure drafts, and information on costs needed to produce these brochures.
    - Brochures 1990 (Box-folder 9:1)
    - Brochures: Costs 1990 (Box-folder 9:2)
    - Brochures: Drafts and Proofs 1990 (Box-folder 9:3)
  - Media Announcements 1980-2000
    This sub-series contains press releases and announcements, public service announcements, media contact lists, and various correspondence related to advertising and public relations for the Norfolk Forum.
    - Media Announcements 1981 (Box-folder 9:4)
    - Media Announcements 1982 (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Media Announcements 1983 (Box-folder 9:6)
    - Media Announcements 1984 (Box-folder 9:7)
    - Media Announcements 1985 (Box-folder 9:8)
    - Media Announcements 1986 (Box-folder 9:9)
    - Media Announcements 1987 (Box-folder 9:10)
    - Media Announcements 1988 (Box-folder 9:11)
    - Media Announcements 1989 (Box-folder 9:12)
    - Media Announcements 1990 (Box-folder 9:13)
    - Media Announcements 1991 (Box-folder 9:14)
    - Media Announcements 1992 (Box-folder 9:15)
    - Media Announcements 1993 (Box-folder 9:16)
    - Media Announcements 1994 (Box-folder 9:17)
    - Media Announcements 1995 (Box-folder 9:18)
    - Media Contacts undated (Box-folder 9:19)
    - Public Relations 1980-1990 (Box-folder 9:20)
    - Public Relations 1990-2000 (Box-folder 9:21)
  - News Clippings 1930-
    This sub-series contains news clippings, editorials, and announcements in the newspaper related to the Norfolk Forum and its events and speakers from the 1930's to the present time. Also included in this sub-series is an index of articles related to the Norfolk Forum from 1947 to 1997. Newspaper clippings related specifically to Norfolk Forum Speakers are located with the appropriate speaker in Series V. Speakers, Sub-series A. Forum Speakers.
    - Editorials 1950-1960 (Box-folder 10:1)
    - Editorials 1960-1970 (Box-folder 10:2)
    - Editorials 1970-1980 (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Editorials 1990-2000 (Box-folder 10:4)
    - Forum Speakers 1930-1940 (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Forum Speakers 1940-1950 (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Forum Speakers 1950-1960 (Box-folder 10:7)
    - Forum Speakers 1960-1970 (Box-folder 10:8)
    - Forum Speakers 1970-1980 (Box-folder 10:9)
    - Forum Speakers 1980-1990 (Box-folder 10:10)
    - Forum Calendars / Announcements 1930-1940 (Box-folder 10:11)
    - Forum Calendars / Announcements 1940-1950 (Box-folder 10:12)
    - Forum Calendars / Announcements 1950-1960 (Box-folder 10:13)
    - Forum Calendars / Announcements 1960-1970 (Box-folder 10:14)
    - Forum Calendars / Announcements 1970-1980 (Box-folder 10:15)
    - Forum Calendars / Announcements 1980-1990 (Box-folder 10:16)
    - Forum Calendars / Announcements 1990-2000 (Box-folder 10:17)
    - Forum Calendars / Announcements 2000- (Box-folder 10:18)
    - List of Articles related to the Norfolk Forum 1947-1997 (Box-folder 10:19)
    - Various Articles 1940-1950 (Box-folder 10:20)
    - Various Articles 1960-1970 (Box-folder 10:21)
- Speakers 1942-2005
  This series is broken into three sub-series related to actual and prospective Norfolk Forum Speakers.
  - Forum Speakers 1942-2003
    This sub-series contains information on Norfolk Forum Speakers including biographical and background material; business, speaker contracts, and correspondence; newspaper clippings, and speeches introducing the speakers. The majority of the speakers represented are from the 1980's to the present time, with a few speakers from the 1970's. For information on earlier speakers, see Series IV. Publicity, Sub-series C. News Clippings.
    Alphabetical by speaker's last name
    - Debate: Mary Matalin and James Carville -- Biography and Background undated (Box-folder 11:1)
    - Debate: Mary Matalin and James Carville -- News Clippings 1995 (Box-folder 11:2)
    - Debate: Mary Matalin and James Carville -- Business and Correspondence 1994-1995 (Box-folder 11:3)
    - Debate: Phyllis Schlafly and Sarah Weddington -- Introduction 14 November 1989 (Box-folder 11:4)
    - Debate: Phyllis Schlafly and Sarah Weddington -- News Clippings November 1989 (Box-folder 11:5)
    - Abend, Hallett -- Introduction 7 January 1943 (Box-folder 11:6)
    - Adler, Mortimer -- Business and Correspondence 1983 (Box-folder 11:7)